<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Audio Visualizer</string>
    <string name="device_access_mic">Start Recording</string>
    <string name="device_access_mic_muted">Stop Recording</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Switch Visualization</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="policy_content">
        <![CDATA[
        <p>
            This policy governs the manner in which Projapps collects, uses, maintains and
            discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the Audio Visualizer
            app ("App").
        </p>
        <u>Personal identification information</u>
        <p>
            We do not collect personal identification information from Users of our App.
        </p>
        <u>Non-personal identification information</u>
        <p>
            We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they
            interact with our App. Non-personal identification information may include the pattern
            of usage, the type of device and technical information about Users means of access to
            our App, such as the operating system and the service providers utilized and other
            similar information.
        </p>
        <u>How we use collected information</u>
        <p>
            Projapps may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:<br>
            - To improve our App<br>
            - To personalize user experience
        </p>
        <u>How we protect your information</u>
        <p>
            We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security
            measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction
            of your transaction information and data stored on our App.
        </p>
        <u>Sharing your personal information</u>
        <p>
            We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others.
        </p>
        <u>Changes to this privacy policy</u>
        <p>
            Projapps has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we
            will inform via an update of our App.
        </p>
        <u>Your acceptance of these terms</u>
        <p>
            By using this App, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to
            this policy, please do not use our App. Your continued use of the App following the
            posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
        </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
</resources>
